Guide to the McKinney Family Papers, 1823-1964
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES VI. Ida DeEtte Ford McKinney
  - Letter to Ida from Angie [ schoolmate], 18 Feb 1869 (Folder 10.37)
  - Letter from Ida to her mother [Pittsfield, PA], 30 May 1871 (Folder 10.38)
  - Program for "The Merchant of Venice" with Mrs. J.L. McKinney as Portia, 17 July 1881 (Folder 10.39)
  - Music concert programs, compliments of Mrs. John L. McKinney, 28 July 1886 (Folder 10.40)
  - Mrs. J. L. McKinney's visiting cards, undated (Folder 10.41)
  - Letter to Ethel McKinney from Ida with envelope, 13 Aug 1886 (Folder 10.42)
  - Booklet of the Shakespearean Club, 1886-1887 (Folder 10.43)
  - Letter to Glenn from Ida (Mother), 19 Jan 1888 (Folder 10.44)
  - Letter to (Ethelyn) from Ida, undated (Folder 10.45)
  - Prescription for Ida, undated (Folder 10.46)
  - Letter to Ethelyn and Glenn from Ida [The Jackson Sanatorium, NY], 1892 (Folder 10.47)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from Ida, [1892] (Folder 10.48)
  - Letter to "My Poor Darling: [?] from Ida, 7 Apr 1894 (Folder 10.49)
  - Letter to Glenn and Ethelyn from J. L. McKinney, 8 May 1894 (Folder 10.50)
  - Ida Ford McKinney's Obituaries, 1984 (Folder 10.51)
  - Clipping re: Main Street Shakespeare Club, undated (Folder 10.52)
  - Notes on the life of Ida McKinney, undated (Folder 10.53)
  - Photo of Ida Ford McKinney and photo of her grave, undated (Folder 10.54)
- SERIES VII. Glenn Ford McKinney
  - Glenn Ford McKinney
    - Photo of Glenn Ford McKinney's Birthplace, 1914 (Folder 11.1)
    - The American Railway by Glenn Ford McKinney, undated (Folder 11.2)
    - The Power of Ideas. Oration by Glenn F. McKinney, 10 Feb 1886 (Folder 11.3)
    - Invitation to Titusville H.S. Commencement Exercises by the Class of 1886, undated (Folder 11.4)
    - Program for Titusville H.S. Commencement (Glenn's graduation), 18 June 1886 (Folder 11.5)
    - Invitation to Closing Exercises of the Hill School, 15 June 1887 (Folder 11.6)
    - Letter of admission to Glenn from the College of New Jersey, 27 June 1887 (Folder 11.7)
    - Essay by Glenn on the Panama Canal, 30 Mar 1889 (Folder 11.8)
    - Poem; song about Canadohta Lake, 29 May-2 June 1889 (Folder 11.9)
    - Invitation to Reception for Senior Class at Princeton, 18 June 1889 (Folder 11.10)
    - Tributes to Geoffrey Chaucer and Thomas B. Macaulay by G. F. McKinney, [late 1880s-early 1890s?] (Folder 11.11)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney with envelope, 17 Feb 1891 (Folder 11.12)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney with envelope, 9 Mar 1891 (Folder 11.13)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney with envelope, [28 Apr 1891?] (Folder 11.14)
    - The College of NJ's honor list for the class of 1891 and commencement program, 3 June 1891 (Folder 11.15)
    - Princeton Class Day Program for Class of 1891, 8 June 1891 (Folder 11.16)
    - Princeton University Class of 1891 Book (published Feb 17, 1934), 17 Feb 1934 (Folder 11.17)
    - 2 G. F. McKinney visiting cards, 17 Feb 1934 (Folder 11.17)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney [The Manhattan Athletic Club], 3 Mar 1892 (Folder 11.18)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney, [9 May 1892?] (Folder 11.19)
    - Program for the New York Law School Commencement; clipping re: commencement, 7 June 1893; undated (Folder 11.20)
    - G. F. McKinney visiting card, undated (Folder 11.20)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney with envelope, 15 Feb 1894 (Folder 11.21)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney, 19 Feb 1894 (Folder 11.22)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney with envelope [New York], 11 June 1894 (Folder 11.23)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney with envelope [New York], 18 June 1894 (Folder 11.24)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney with envelope [New York], 20 June 1894 (Folder 11.25)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney with envelope [New York], 28 June 1894 (Folder 11.26)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney with envelope [New York], 9 July 1894 (Folder 11.27)
    - J. L. McKinney's Journal, Aug-Sept 1895 (Folder 11.28)
    - Photo of J. L. McKinney, undated (Folder 11.28)
    - The Titusville Morning Clipping re: G.F. McKinney's disappearance from hunting party, Sept 1895 (Folder 11.29)
    - Copy of New York Herald article re: G. F. McKinney disappearance, 16 Sept 1895 (Folder 11.30)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from N. Wentworth re: G. F. McKinney's disappearance [Randolph, NY], 19 Sept 1895 (Folder 11.31)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney with business card [New York], 15 Oct 1895 (Folder 11.32)
    - Letter to (Ethelyn?) from G. F. McKinney [New York], 19 Oct 1895 (Folder 11.33)
    - Letter to (Ethelyn?) from G. F. McKinney [New York], 28 Oct 1895 (Folder 11.34)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney [New York], 31 Oct 1895 (Folder 11.35)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney [New York], 11 Nov 1895 (Folder 11.36)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney [New York], 30 Jan 1896 (Folder 11.37)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney [New York], 30 Apr 1896 (Folder 11.38)
    - Certificate granted to G. F. McKinney as Attorney Proctor, Solicitor, Counselor and Advocate, 22 Dec 1896 (Folder 11.39)
    - Card from Clerk W.H. Shankland acknowledging admission to practice as an Attorney and Counselor at Law, 6 Oct 1898 (Folder 11.40)
    - Photos of "Killieburn" estate in Westchester County, NY, 24 Dec 1899 (Folder 11.41)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 6 Nov 1903 (Folder 11.42)
    - Letter to Grandma Ford from G. F. McKinney [New York], 20 Apr 1904 (Folder 11.43)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney with envelope, 21 Sept 1905 (Folder 11.44)
    - Timeline of significant events in G.F. McKinney's life, undated (Folder 11.45)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney with envelope [New York], 22 Apr 1907 (Folder 11.46)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 6 Jan 1908 (Folder 11.47)
    - Letter to "Mac" from Alexander Reading Gulick, undated (Folder 12.1)
    - Letter to G. F. McKinney from the Princeton Club, 21 Jan 1908 (Folder 12.2)
    - Letter to G. F. McKinney from H.R. Charlton [Bronxville, NY], 8 Feb 1908 (Folder 12.3)
    - Letter to G. F. McKinney from J. L. McKinney, 21 Apr 1908 (Folder 12.4)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [White Plains, NY], 24 Jan 1909 (Folder 12.5)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [White Plains, NY], 22 Feb 1909 (Folder 12.6)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 26 Feb 1909 (Folder 12.7)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 15 Feb 1910 (Folder 12.8)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney with envelope [New York], 17 May 1910 (Folder 12.9)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 21 June 1910 (Folder 12.10)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 23 June 1910 (Folder 12.11)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 14 Dec 1910 (Folder 12.12)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 16 Dec 1910 (Folder 12.13)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 27 Dec 1910 (Folder 12.14)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney with envelope [New York], 8 Feb 1911 (Folder 12.15)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney with envelope [New York], 27 Feb 1911 (Folder 12.16)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney with envelope [New York], 8 Mar 1911 (Folder 12.17)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 8 Mar 1911 (Folder 12.18)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney with envelope [New York], 14 Apr 1911 (Folder 12.19)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney with envelope [New York], 19 Apr 1911 (Folder 12.20)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney with envelope [New York], 4 May 1911 (Folder 12.21)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney with envelope [New York], 6 June 1911 (Folder 12.22)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 8 Feb 1912 (Folder 12.23)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 8 Feb 1912 (Folder 12.24)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 21 Feb 1912 (Folder 12.25)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 5 Mar 1912 (Folder 12.26)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 6 May 1912 (Folder 12.27)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 13 May 1912 (Folder 12.28)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 15 May 1912 (Folder 12.29)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 16 May 1912 (Folder 12.30)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 21 May 1912 (Folder 12.31)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney with envelope [Eccles Hotel, Glengarriff, Cork], 25 July 1912 (Folder 12.32)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [Gweedore Hotel, Co, Denegal], Summer 1912 (Folder 12.33)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [Killerney], 30 July 1912 (Folder 12.34)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [Gweedore Hotel], 19 Aug 1912 (Folder 12.35)
    - Envelope [Gweedore Hotel], 22 Aug 1912 (Folder 12.36)
    - Telegram to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [France], 23 Aug 1912 (Folder 12.36)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney with envelope [New York], 30 Sept 1912 (Folder 12.37)
    - Deposits for Ida McKinney and J. L. McKinney, 21 Oct 1912 (Folder 12.38)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney, 26 Dec 1912 (Folder 12.39)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 30 Dec 30, 1912 (Folder 12.40)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], Jan 7. 1913 (Folder 12.41)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney with records of stocks, 17 Jan 1913 (Folder 12.42)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney with envelope, 21 Jan 1913 (Folder 12.43)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 4 Mar 1913 (Folder 12.44)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 5 Mar 1913 (Folder 12.45)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney with memorandum of stocks to sell [New York], 6 Mar 1913 (Folder 12.46)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney, 10 Mar 1913 (Folder 12.47)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 13 Mar 1913 (Folder 12.48)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 15 Mar-17 Mar 1913 (Folder 12.49)
    - Sketch of boats, fishes, and rocks on Titusville Commercial Bank Stationary, undated (Folder 12.50)
    - Letter to J. L. McKinney from G. F. McKinney [New York], 11 Apr-7 May 1913 (Folder 12.51)
    - Map of Tourilli Fish and Game Club, 1913 (Folder 12.52)
    - G. F. McKinney's Passport with 2 name cards, 20 Aug 1914 (Folder 12.53)
    - "A Curious Experience" by Theodore Roosevelt, [post-1915?] (Folder 12.54)
    - Bill from Acker Merrall & Condit Company [New York], Feb 1916 (Folder 12.55)
    - Letter to Miss McKinney [from Alexander Lambell?], 9 Nov 1916 (Folder 12.56)
    - Christmas card from G. F. McKinney, 1916 (Folder 12.57)
    - G. F. McKinney's license to carry firearms, 21 June 1917 (Folder 12.58)
    - Letters to Jeannie from G. F. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 19 July-4 Sept 1917 (Folder 12.59)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney with envelope [La Grangeville, NY], 16 Apr 1918 (Folder 12.60)
    - Letter to Jeannie from J. L. McKinney [Chateau Frontenac, Quebec], 23 Aug 1918 (Folder 12.61)
    - Letter to Jeannie from J. L. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 31 Dec 1918 and 30 Jan 1919 (Folder 12.62)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney and card addressed to P.G. Stamm and Co. [Tulsa, OK], 14 Feb 1921 (Folder 13.1)
    - Letters to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney [New York], 8 Apr-9 Apr 1921 (Folder 13.2)
    - Receipt for G. F. McKinney from the New York State Bar Association, 18 Apr 1921 (Folder 13.3)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney [New York], 18 May 1921 (Folder 13.4)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, New York], 16 Dec 1921 (Folder 13.5)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney [La Grangeville. NY], 7 Feb 1922 (Folder 13.6)
    - Instruction manual for De Laval's Cream Separators, undated (Folder 13.7)
    - Card for Jean McKinney re: McKinney Limestone Mill in La Grangeville, NY, 10 Feb 1922 (Folder 13.8)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney [New York], 23 Feb 1922 (Folder 13.9)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], Spring 1922 (Folder 13.10)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney [On board the "Virginia"], 18 June 1922 (Folder 13.11)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney [Bay of the Islands], 24 June 1922 (Folder 13.12)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney with envelope [Quebec], 2 July 1922 (Folder 13.13)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 2 Aug 1922 (Folder 13.14)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from Aileen, [1 Aug 1922?] (Folder 13.15)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 3 Jan 1923 (Folder 13.16)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 7 Feb 1923 (Folder 13.17)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 11 Mar 1923 (Folder 13.18)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney with picture of a black hen, [1923] (Folder 13.19)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney [New York], 4 Oct 1923 (Folder 13.20)
    - Acceptance into Princeton Chapter of Phi Beta Kappa Society, 13 Mar 1924 (Folder 13.21)
    - Photographs of G. F. McKinney, 1890 and 1924; (2) (Folder 13.21)
    - Letter to Professor Robert Scoon from G. F. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, NY], 25 Mar 1924 (Folder 13.22)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney [Hotel La Salle, NY], 25 Mar 1924 (Folder 13.23)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney [New York], 28 Mar 1924 (Folder 13.24)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 24 Apr 1924 (Folder 13.25)
    - Valentine to G. F. McKinney from (Jean) [Greenwich, Conn.], 13 Feb 1925 (Folder 13.26)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney [Chateau Frontenac, Quebec], 15 June 1925 (Folder 13.27)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney, 28 June 1925 (Folder 13.28)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney with envelope, 20 July 1926 (Folder 13.29)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney [New York], 30 Oct 1925; 16 Dec 1925 (Folder 13.30)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney [New York], 8 Apr 1926 (Folder 13.31)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney [New York], 22 Mar 1927 (Folder 13.32)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 24 Mar 1927 (Folder 13.33)
    - Easter Card for Jean from G. F. McKinney [New York], 15 Apr 1927 (Folder 13.34)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney, 9 July 1927 (Folder 13.35)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney [Titusville, PA], 6 Mar 1928 (Folder 13.36)
    - Letters to G. F. McKinney from the president of The American Museum of Natural History [New York], 30 Nov 1928; 10 Dec 1928; (2) (Folder 13.37)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney [New York], 16 Aug 1929 (Folder 13.38)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney [New York], 27 Feb 1930 (Folder 13.39)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney with envelope [Southern Pines, NC], 7 Mar 1930 (Folder 13.40)
    - Letter to Jean from G. F. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], [Oct 1932] (Folder 13.41)
    - Map of Camp McKinney in Southern Pines, NC, undated (Folder 13.42)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney [La Grangeville, NY], 29 May 1933 (Folder 13.43)
    - Letter to Ethelyn from (Aileen) [Southern Pines, NC], [Jan or Feb 1934] (Folder 13.44)
    - Clippings re: Death of G. F. McKinney, Feb 1934 (Folder 13.45)
    - Telegram for Ethelyn from Clarence Woolley, 15 Feb 1934 (Folder 13.46)
    - Short biographical information on G. F. McKinney, undated (Folder 13.47)
    - Obituary for G. F. McKinney in The Princeton Alumni Weekly, Vol. XXXIV, No. 27, 6 Apr 1934 (Folder 13.48)
    - Clipping re: James R. Taylor's election as vice president of the National Fuel Gas Company, undated (Folder 13.49)
    - Last Will and Testament of G. F. McKinney [New York], 5 Mar 1934 (Folder 13.50)
    - Union Vale Bicentennial Committee Commemorative Booklet, 1976 (Folder 13.51)
    - G. F. McKinney's Log Book for Tanya, 1908-1909 (Folder 13.52)
    - Partial photocopies collection of G. F. McKinney's correspondence, 1922-1928 (Folder 13.53)
    - Release of Dower from Annette Reynaud McKinney to G. F. McKinney, 1915 (Folder 13.54)
  - Jean Webster to Glenn Ford McKinney
    - Card to G. F. McKinney from Jean Webster, 1909 (Folder 29.1)
    - Letters to G. F. McKinney from Jean Webster, 1910 (Folder 29.2)
    - Letters to G. F. McKinney from Jean Webster, 1911 (Folder 29.3)
    - Letters to G. F. McKinney from Jean Webster, 1912 (Folder 29.4)
    - Letters to G. F. McKinney from Jean Webster, March-June 1913 (Folder 29.5)
    - Letters to G. F. McKinney from Jean Webster, July 1913 (Folder 29.6)
    - Letters to G. F. McKinney from Jean Webster, Aug 1913 (Folder 29.7)
    - Letters to G. F. McKinney from Jean Webster, Sept-Dec 1913 (Folder 29.8)
    - Letters to G. F. McKinney from Jean Webster, Jan-Feb 1914 (Folder 29.9)
    - Letters to G. F. McKinney from Jean Webster, Mar-May 1914 (Folder 29.10)
    - Letters to G. F. McKinney from Jean Webster, June-July 1914 (Folder 29.11)
    - Letters to G. F. McKinney from Jean Webster, Aug-Sept 1914 (Folder 29.12)
- SERIES VIII. Ethelyn McKinney
  - Program for the 4th Annual Picnic of the Main Street Shakespeare Club, 24 June 1884 (Folder 14.1)
  - List of names from Beedes Camp, 31 July 1886 (Folder 14.2)
  - Invitation to the 37th Annual Commencement at Titusville High School with name card for Miss Edith Cadwallader, 17 June 1887 (Folder 14.3)
  - Letter to Ethel from Elema, 25 Dec 1889 (Folder 14.4)
  - Program to Cecilia Quartette Recital at Smith College of Music, 8 Jan 1890 (Folder 14.5)
  - Record of Games of the Hill School Nine (G. F. McKinney's baseball team), 1887 (Folder 14.6)
  - Letter to Ethelyn from Isabel M. Coffin and Kate with envelope, Oct 1891 (Folder 14.7)
  - Name cards for Mr. W. Christy Bryan and Mr. Wm. Russel Deemer, Oct 1891; (2) (Folder 14.7)
  - Clipping re: "Promenade at Princeton", Oct 1891 (Folder 14.7)
  - "The Farmer Boy" poem, Oct 1891 (Folder 14.8)
  - Program for Abend Unterhaltung II at Smith College School of Music, 29 Nov 1892 (Folder 14.9)
  - Program for Much Ado About Nothing presented by The Wallace House Dramatic Society, 1 Mar 1893 (Folder 14.10)
  - Poem written by Ethelyn for Sophia A. Wills, 12 Mar 1893 (Folder 14.11)
  - Tickets for the World's Columbian Exposition, 9 Oct 1893; (2) (Folder 14.12)
  - Name cards, 9 Oct 1893; (3) (Folder 14.12)
  - Telegram for Ethelyn from L.G. Bigelow, 1 Dec 1893 (Folder 14.13)
  - Program Exercise Commemorative of Richard Wagner by Smith College School of Music, 6 Dec 1893 (Folder 14.14)
  - Envelope addressed to Ethelyn from G. F. McKinney, 19 July 1894 (Folder 14.15)
  - Programs for Achilles in Scyros and review of the play, 16 Jan 1895; (5) (Folder 14.16)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Mabel H. Cummings of Wallace House re: Ethelyn's performance, 20 Jan 1895 (Folder 14.17)
  - Advertisement for A Midsummer Night's Dream and 4 newspaper reviews, 14-15 June 1895 (Folder 14.18)
  - Letter to [?] from Ethelyn at Grandma Ford's house [Titusville, PA], 1 July 1896 (Folder 14.19)
  - Poison pen letter from Presbyterian minister, 19 Oct [1886?] (Folder 14.20)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream Program, 17 Dec 1896 (Folder 14.21)
  - New York Herald Cartoons and clipping re: performance of A Midsummer Night's Dream by Smith College girls, 3 Jan 1897 (Folder 14.22)
  - Letter to shareholders of Natural Gas Trust from John Bushnell, 15 Mar 1897 (Folder 14.23)
  - Poem "To a Butterfly" for Ethelyn from L.M.W. (Lena Weinstein), 21 May 1897 (Folder 14.24)
  - Pressed flowers/ check to Morris Baily from Ethelyn, Apr-June 1897 (Folder 14.25)
  - Receipt from Vente and Achat de Lirres, Gravures, Fleurs, 21 Dec 1899 (Folder 14.26)
  - Picture of flowers - XL Club, 14 Mar 1898 (Folder 14.27)
  - Picture of flowers - Picture of Cupid, 14 Feb 1898 (Folder 14.27)
  - Letter to Col. W.R. Holloway from Oram Perry with business card [Indianapolis], 5 May 1898 (Folder 14.28)
  - Letter to Alliene from [?] [Hotel Cecil, Strand, W.C.], [1898] (Folder 14.29)
  - Mementos of Glasgow, 3 July 1898 (Folder 14.30)
  - Letter to Mother and Ethelyn from (Glenn) [Cunard R.M.S. "Luciana"], 3 July 1898 (Folder 14.31)
  - Letters to [?] from Ethelyn McKinney [The Howard Hotel, London], 22 and 24 July 1898 (Folder 14.32)
  - Card from Ethelyn to [?] [Howard Hotel, London], 28 July 1898 (Folder 14.33)
  - Letter to Mrs. John C. Ford from Ethelyn with envelope, 11 Aug 1898 (Folder 14.34)
  - Poster for Grasmere and Lake District Athletic Sports, 18 Aug 1898 (Folder 14.35)
  - Letter to Grandma from Ethelyn with envelope, 19 Aug 1898 (Folder 14.36)
  - Letter to [?] from (Ethelyn) [Hotel Salisbury], 30 Aug 1898 (Folder 14.37)
  - Letter to [?] from Ethelyn [The Howard Hotel, London], 2 Sept 1898 (Folder 14.38)
  - Photo of Ethelyn and her friends in Vollendam, Sept 1898 (Folder 14.39)
  - Letter to family from Ethelyn [Dresden, Germany], 27 Oct 1898 (Folder 14.40)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ethelyn with 4 leaf clover [Dresden, Germany], 3 Nov 1898 (Folder 14.41)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ethelyn, 10 Nov 1898 (Folder 14.42)
  - Birthday card from Ethelyn [Dresden, Germany], 29 Nov 1898 (Folder 14.43)
  - Letter to (J. L. McKinney?) from Ethelyn, 4 Dec 1898 (Folder 14.44)
  - Letter to family from Ethelyn [Dresden, Germany], 13 Dec 1898 (Folder 14.45)
  - Letter to Grandmother from Ethelyn [Dresden, Germany], 20 Dec 1898 (Folder 14.46)
  - Sketches of Eastern religious symbols, [1898] (Folder 14.47)
  - Letter to family from Ethelyn [Dresden, Germany], 11 Jan 1899 (Folder 14.48)
  - Letter to Grandma Ford from Ethelyn [Dresden, Germany], 20 Feb 1899 (Folder 14.49)
  - Letter to Grandma Ford from Ethelyn [Germany], 26 Feb 1899 (Folder 14.50)
  - Card for Mrs. John C. Ford from Ethelyn [Italy], 26 Mar 1899 (Folder 14.51)
  - Letter to family from Ethelyn [Paris], 23 June 1899 (Folder 14.52)
  - Receipt from J.C. Cording and Co. Waterproofers, 28 July 1899 (Folder 14.53)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ethelyn with envelope, 14 Aug 1899 (Folder 14.54)
  - Letter to Aunt Fonte from (Ethelyn) [Edinburgh, Scotland], 28 Aug 1899 (Folder 14.55)
  - Map of North British Railway, 1900 (Folder 14.56)
  - "Scotch-spirit" picture, [1899?] (Folder 14.56)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ethelyn with envelope and small photo of Ethelyn among Scotch thistles, 1899 (Folder 14.57)
  - 2 part latter to Grandma Ford from Ethelyn [Oxford an Winchester, England], 17 and 20 Sept 1899 (Folder 14.58)
  - Receipt from Vital Franses Freres Jewelers [Paris], 3 Oct 1899 (Folder 14.59)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ethelyn with envelope [Paris], 12 Oct 1899 (Folder 14.60)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ethelyn with envelope [Paris], 3 Nov 1899 (Folder 15.1)
  - Letter to family from Ethelyn [Paris], 10 Nov 1899 (Folder 15.2)
  - Receipt from C. Guillol [Paris], 11 Nov 1899 (Folder 15.3)
  - Letter to Grandma Ford from Ethelyn with envelope [Paris], 16 Nov 1899 (Folder 15.4)
  - Envelope addressed to Glenn Ford McKinney [Paris], 24 Nov 1899 (Folder 15.5)
  - Program for Chatelet [Paris], 1900-1901 (Folder 15.6)
  - Card for [Gertrude?] [Paris], [1899?] (Folder 15.7)
  - Letter to Grandma Ford from Ethelyn with envelope [Paris], 5 Dec [1899?] (Folder 15.8)
  - Letter to J. L. McKinney from Ethelyn [Paris], [1899] (Folder 15.9)